<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Investing - Tag - Pranesh Srinivasan</title>
        <link>http://spranesh.github.io/tags/investing/</link>
        <description>Investing - Tag - Pranesh Srinivasan</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>spranesh@gmail.com (Pranesh Srinivasan)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>spranesh@gmail.com (Pranesh Srinivasan)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 09:59:26 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://spranesh.github.io/tags/investing/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Survey of non-food FMCGs</title>
    <link>http://spranesh.github.io/posts/2017-02-04-fmcg/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 09:59:26 -0800</pubDate>
    <author>Pranesh Srinivasan</author>
    <guid>http://spranesh.github.io/posts/2017-02-04-fmcg/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Fast moving consumer goods (FMCGs) are an essential part of our lives today.
Not all FMCGs are commodities however. Some brands continue to engage a loyal
and growing user base due to superior products, global outreach, and decades of
advertising. Colgate is synonymous for the entire dental care industry, as Gillette is for
men&rsquo;s hygiene.</p>
<p>A billion people are being added to the middle class over the next decade.
Purchasing power continues to grow and demographics continue to be favourable.
We have more single person households than ever before. At the same time, there
is disruption happening at an unprecedented scale. Whether it&rsquo;s better online
distribution like the <a href="http://www.dollarshaveclub.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Dollar Shave Club</a> or a
growing number of white label products, moats that were considered unbreachable
have started to chip away.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Why equities?</title>
    <link>http://spranesh.github.io/posts/2015-10-22-why-equities/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Pranesh Srinivasan</author>
    <guid>http://spranesh.github.io/posts/2015-10-22-why-equities/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>In this post, we look at long-term inflation adjust returns across six
different asset classes - cash, residential housing, gold, industrial
commodities, bonds, and stocks (equities). By long-term, we mean at least a
century or more.</p>
<p>In doing so, we shall find that equity ownership in cash flow producing
businesses via stocks outperform all other categories.  All charts in this post
deal with real returns - i.e, returns adjusted for inflation.</p>]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
